Miss Kobayashi, Miss Kobayashi!
If someone asked, you say I'm the ultimate maid, right?
No, of course I wouldn't. What are you up to?
You're wrong. I think I'm the ultimate maid,
and that's the only thing that matters.
So pretty.
Hold on. Look at this book I found.
A maid cafe's opening? And it's close, too.
It says all who enter will be welcomed by the best maids.
Best maids? But how?
Who do they think they are making such false claims without me?
That's right. No one should make false claims,
including the dragon in front of me currently making them.
Then I'll just turn the cafe to ash,
and their business will fail as a result of my cursed flame!
Your literal burning love?
I highly advise against it.
Noted! I'm going to scout out the enemy!
I wonder if Toru's okay.
I've returned from the mortal beyond!
Welcome home. How'd it go? Did you destroy anything?
Of course not! I wound up getting a job there!
How?
I proudly stormed the enemy's evil den to find their leader.
There's an evil den?
Fear me!
Oh, are you here to interview for the new maid job?
You're awfully presumptuous wearing a maid outfit already.
You're pretty, though.
And I love your positive attitude.
You were hired.
Yay!
And that's how we returned home victorious.
They call that an interview? They're screwed.
I've had a lot of free time on my hands lately since you and Kana are always out.
I need to fill it somehow.
You're like a bored housewife getting a job for fun.
So you're serious about doing this?
Can you handle it?
What are you talking about?
I gladly work as a maid every day of my life for free.
I'm used to it now.
Don't.
Toru, I may have a job at a bigger company now.
But when I was living with my parents, I worked at a restaurant.
Trust me, don't underestimate the service industry.
Ms. Kapiyoshi!
Don't get me wrong.
Cosplay maids at maid cafes offend me in ways I can't even get into.
But their customer service is worthy of respect.
This is a great opportunity, Toru.
It'll be good for you to learn about the service industry.
You look scary when you point like that.
Well, it's been a while since we had that conversation.
I wonder how Toru's doing at her new job.
Kobayashi, you're a worrywart.
Is this it?
Hello, and welcome home, my master.
And welcome, young lady.
Lots of people dress like Lady Toru.
Interesting design.
Looks like this cafe went with plain style maids.
People don't use the word moe very much anymore,
but they've definitely kept the essence of those times in their theme.
Let's check out the menu.
Oh, this is also true to those roots.
There's a special service with every menu item.
I'm betting the magic chants, like,
filled by tummy with much yummy are different for each as well.
You know a lot, Kobayashi.
I'm gonna tell you a secret, Kana.
One time, long ago, I tried working in a cafe like this.
It didn't work out.
I don't get it, but I'm sorry.
Wait a minute, where's Toru?
Back there.
Hmm?
Table ten, your order's up!
On it!
I'm running low on plates, so let's get some out fast!
Right away!
Hmm?
Ah!
Incredible!
Way to go ahead, Chef!
Thanks for everything you do to help us, Chef!
Chef Toru's the best!
No, thank you!
I'm grateful to have a team who works together so efficiently!
Bye, Ms. Kobayashi!
You came to see me?
Wow, you're doing a great job.
I'm truly surprised.
Told you I was the best!
It's actually been quite easy for me to handle.
I've taken another step forward as a maid.
Except...
I'm not working as a maid at all!
You're a chef.
I'm gonna get someone on the floor to switch with me!
I actually think they put you in the right position.
It's the right position for a volcanic dragon!
Please go out and come back in again!
Huh?
Time to turn delicious now!
It's good!
Greetings!
Welcome, Kobayashi!
You're supposed to say master!
When head chef first started on the floor, she said,
I refuse to call anyone master but Ms. Kobayashi.
That's weird, because she doesn't call me master at home ever.
Will you please have a seat in our comfy booth?
You mean I can finally order something?
Omarice, please.
Kimmy, Omarice.
Okay.
Two Omarices.
Sure!
They'll be out in a flash!
Now I have to perform a spell to make it super delicious!
Make it adorable.
Okay!
I call upon the Shadow King who rules this world!
Make this the greatest it can be with your dark arts!
I beseech thee for quality worthy of praise!
Raise its value and bring forth a monument to your glory!
Let my magic spread and bring corruption!
Let my ideals erode the world and bring mass chaos!
Replace all that is organic with palatable falsehood!
Be ever so delicious!
Mooi, mooi, kyuns!
Yummy to the dummy!
I hope you like it!
He used actual magic, a curse in fact!
So good!
Bring me the head chef!
Hello there!
I am your head chef, maid, and of course dragon,
Tauru the Great!
Okay, she's got talent, but is it enough?
I don't want to be anyone's maid but Ms. Kobayashi,
so I'm gonna quit.
Thank you.
You can't!
Don't do that to us!
Our cafes become famous because of the taste of the recipes you created!
There are so many posts spreading about it online by word of mouth!
Head chef, don't!
Head chef!
Well, maybe I'll teach you the magic chant
so you can make your food delicious after I'm gone!
Make notes!
In order for a human to do it,
first you'll have to draw this magic circle.
Good afternoon and welcome home, my master!
Oh my, what a nice cafe!
We'll take two Oma Rices!
Yes, sir, coming right up!
Here we go!
Now I'll cast a spell to make it delicious!
I call upon the Shadow King that rules this world!
Make this dish the greatest it can be with your dark arts!
I think this is the most unique maid cafe I've ever been to!
Worthy of praise!
I am a maid, not a chef!
Where all the rave reviews about me is a maid!
Give me a favor and spare the mouse.
We predict sudden changes in the weather throughout the day,
so please stay tuned for developing reports.
Next up is the news.
There was a large-scale landslide early this morning.
Whoa.
It looks like part of the Earth was sliced away...
It's the mountain where I met you, Toru.
That's weird.
How could they do that to our precious sacred spot?
I'll find the culprit behind this and send them to Jahana and Jahanam!
Then I'll crush their bones and beat them to a man!
But the only ones who could do something like that are...
It couldn't possibly be me.
I was reviewing the new parameters for a game event at that time.
Lukawa's been out of the country since yesterday.
And fortunately, I always know where she is because we're bound.
We're bound by magic.
It's so good! Delicious!
Ow!
What the heck are you doing here, Toru?
You're the culprit!
What are you talking about?
The news.
They mentioned a mountain that was damaged.
Oh, yeah!
I was gonna ask you about the same thing!
Huh?
You're saying it wasn't you?
No, I just assumed it was Toru.
Well, it wasn't!
Hold on.
Then that means it had to be some other dragon that we don't know.
There aren't that many dragons powerful enough to break my barrier.
Then who could it be?
It was me!
Ooh!
Hi!
Elulu.
What a pretty city this is.
There's chatter and laughter everywhere.
With so many people around, you could be indulging in mass destruction.
Yet here you are, Chaos Dragon, chummy with them.
I was watching because I was a little curious and I see what's going on.
I'm not amused.
What I'm trying to say is, you're an enemy now!
Who is that?
Ilulu.
She's with the most radical wing of the Chaos faction and loves destruction.
I'm sure she followed Toru here.
You see what I mean?
She clearly came here to destroy this world.
I see, but I trust that Toru will do something about her.
Miss Kobayashi, Ilulu's might is only slightly below Toru's.
If the two of them fight, they'll destroy this whole region.
I'm sure she'll do something about that too.
You really believe in Toru, huh?
Well, it's not like that.
I have no choice, so I'm embracing it.
Destruction isn't permitted in this world.
Yeah, what's your point?
I'm in the Chaos faction too.
If you can't abide by the rules, I'll have to send you home.
I'm more than happy to fight with you.
Attacks like that will have no effect on me.
No, the city!
I can't tell.
Is she struggling?
Toru's trying to protect the city while fighting, so she's at a disadvantage.
Are you saying you're not going to help her?
I can't.
I'm with the Harmony faction.
Normally, Toru and I would be enemies.
Huh?
I've put up a barrier to keep humans away, but that's just to avoid trouble.
What about the others?
If we asked Sir Fafnir, he would say she needs to clean up her own mess.
Lady Lukula is with the Spectator faction, so she doesn't do intervention, and Kana's not strong enough.
If she defeats Toru, I'll be permitted to fight.
Protecting you and the city aligns with the Harmony faction.
But then, she'd be...
What good is believing in her if it doesn't give her strength?
It's the same as observing and doing nothing.
But what else can I...
Elma!
Please don't try.
I know you want me to jump in and help Toru, but I cannot.
Pudding!
I know what you're trying to do, and you can't just buy me...
Cream puffs!
Coffee jelly!
Chocolate cake!
Naples are a pancake!
Ooh!
Anything sweet you can think of!
Ow!
I just hit you with 30 shots of flaming acid.
That's on top of several nice swipes with my claws.
And you gave it an owl?
Then I'm stumped.
I can't think of a solid way to kill you.
Me neither.
Huh?
If I go all out with an attack, the city will be destroyed.
But I know there's no way to defeat you otherwise.
Your attacks are starting to get really annoying as well.
But I can't do it!
I have to protect the city!
I feel like exploding and taking everything with me!
You're bluffing.
Toru!
Elmo was awesome and put up a barrier!
Only because Miss Kobayashi decided to bribe me!
That's disgusting.
Relying on humans?
Yeah, well, so what?
We're just getting started!
Now to destroy this world with my trauma!
That was a close call.
I didn't take much damage.
But I nearly forgot I had to protect the city, too.
For a moment, I thought about letting everyone else in this world die.
Except Miss Kobayashi.
But then I wouldn't be able to stay here with her.
Miss Kobayashi...
I am...
Wanna go home?
Hmm...
Yeah...
I will fight as hard as I must.
If it means staying with Miss Kobayashi, I can destroy any obstacles that stand in my way.
That human back there.
She got Elma involved and saved Toru.
Humans are our enemies.
That's what we were taught, but there's something about that one.
I want to know more.
Me? Me who?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
A cold, huh?
On the train?
Your bag?
Hmm.
Compensation?
By today?
Two million?
Oh, that's terrible.
It was harder to get that gate open than I expected.
I'm surprised Toru could easily pull off something so draining.
The last train.
I guess I could have Toru come pick me up instead, but she's probably tired.
Or...
It's you.
The human called Kobayashi.
I want to know why you choose to live with a dragon.
Because Toru decided she wanted to stay in my life.
Believe me, I didn't try to convince her.
Aren't you afraid?
Hear me, human!
Hard to be afraid of her when she's so cute most of the time.
Oh.
So she turns you on?
The reason you're not afraid of Toru in her human form is because you're in love with her.
Huh?
Of course not!
What are you talking about?
What a powerful denial.
Suspicious.
That's not it!
Then...
What is this?
Wow.
Well, you're only human in the end, right?
You can't resist your desires.
Go ahead and let your pitiful male instincts run wild and free for once.
You want to be loved, don't you?
Tonight you can finally unleash your lustful longings.
Go on.
Do it!
Get your kicks out of my face!
I'm a woman!
Cut the crap, okay?
Wait, those lumps of flesh do nothing but unleash flames of rage and resentment any time I see them!
Oh, no!
The last train's about to leave!
Wait!
Come back!
Please do not rush to board the train while doors are closing.
Well, what?
Haven't you caused enough commotion?
Mm-hmm.
I cannot accept you.
Huh?
Humans and dragons are never permitted to coexist.
Hmm.
When together, their differences cause suffering.
As that suffering grows, it breeds hatred.
Respect turns to envy.
And eventually creates pain.
What Toru feels for you is not what you think.
It's simply curiosity.
And when that eventually runs out...
Wake up!
Everything's fine.
I was listening, I promise.
You liar!
You were talking about the differences between species or something.
You can't accept me and we shouldn't coexist.
So is there anything a lowly human like myself can do to help you?
Correct your understanding!
Hmm.
Then please allow me to borrow your own words to make an important point.
When we embrace our differences and learn to enjoy them, it breeds love.
Respect is joined by trust and eventually creates a bond.
I never thought I would ever say that about my life with Toru, but it's completely true.
That's just a convenient interpretation.
There are still tragedies, too.
You're glossing over the truth with a bunch of pretty words.
Yeah, you're right.
Huh?
There are times we fight and hurt each other, but I try not to think about it too much.
Some might say I'm repressing anger, but I call it choosing battles.
Even if I don't always understand her feelings, I do what I can to respect them.
And we manage.
I guess it's just the way I am.
Is that how you humans really think?
No, but it is the way that I personally think.
Wouldn't you agree that there's a distinction between the way you and other dragons in your
realm see things?
No, but there's no need to.
We're the same.
Really?
But what about the dragon who came up with these absolute guidelines for how a dragon should
think?
It wasn't you, was it?
You can spout pretty words, but you're still a human.
It didn't work because you're a female.
Whoa!
I guess the Lulu left?
Huh?
You got to be kidding me.
Hmm?
Is that good?
Ah!
The fate of mankind!
It's in jeopardy!
Ms. Kobayashi, aren't you excited?
The love story of me and you is finally continuing!
Is it? Wasn't there a new dragon?
She won't show up anymore.
That's not true.
This week on Who's Rotten?
Leo.